<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist gettext-domain="gnome-shell-extensions">
  <schema path="/org/gnome/shell/extensions/workspace-buttons-with-app-icons/" id="org.gnome.shell.extensions.workspace-buttons-with-app-icons">
    <key type="i" name="wsb-button-spacing">
        <default>2</default>
        <summary>The spacing between the workspace buttons (pixels)</summary>
        <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-button-padding">
        <default>3</default>
        <summary>The spacing inside the workspace buttons - aka padding - (pixels)</summary>
        <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-button-roundness">
        <default>8</default>
        <summary>How round should the buttons be - aka border radius - (pixels)</summary>
        <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="wsb-show-workspace-number">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Whether to show the workspace number all the time</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-number-font-size">
      <default>18</default>
      <summary>The size of the workspace number (pixels)</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-number-horizontal-padding">
      <default>4</default>
      <summary>The padding from the workspace number left and right (pixels)</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-icon-size">
      <default>26</default>
      <summary>The size of each icon (pixels)</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-icon-spacing">
      <default>0</default>
      <summary>The spacing between the icons in each workspace button (pixels)</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-icons-wrapper-horizontal-padding">
      <default>5</default>
      <summary>The space left and right of all the icons as a whole.</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="wsb-desaturate-icons">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Desaturate icons</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="wsb-active-button-background-color">
      <default>"#273600"</default>
      <summary>The background color of the inactive workspace button</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="wsb-inactive-button-background-color">
      <default>"#241f31"</default>
      <summary>The background color of the inactive workspace button</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="wsb-active-workspace-number-background-color">
      <default>"#4e6119"</default>
      <summary>The background color for the number of the active workspace</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="s" name="wsb-inactive-workspace-number-background-color">
      <default>"#3d3846"</default>
      <summary>The background color for the number of the inactive workspace</summary>
      <description></description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="wsb-container-scroll-to-switch-workspace">
      <default>true</default>
      <summary>Enable scrolling on the container to switch workspaces.</summary>
      <description>
        If other extensions allow scrolling anywhere on the panel to switch workspaces, enabling this can result in double inputs (one scroll equals two switches). 
        This option exists to prevent such conflicts by allowing you to toggle this behavior.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="wsb-middle-click-ignores-clicked-workspace">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Middle click always opens overview for the current workspace.</summary>
      <description>
        By default, when you middle click on another workspace, it will first switch to it and then open overview, for whichever workspace was selected.
        This makes it so that until you manually switch to another workspace, middle clicking anywhere in the container opens overview for the current workspace.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key type="b" name="wsb-right-click-ignores-clicked-workspace">
      <default>false</default>
      <summary>Right click always opens window switcher for the current workspace.</summary>
      <description>
        By default, when you right click on another workspace, it will first switch to it and then open the window switcher, for whichever workspace was selected.
        This makes it so that until you manually switch to another workspace, right clicking anywhere in the container opens the window switcher for the current workspace.
      </description>
    </key>
    <key type="i" name="wsb-generate-window-icon-timeout">
      <default>200</default>
      <summary>The time to wait before generating an icon for a newly opened app (ms)</summary>
      <description>
        On Wayland, with apps opened under the xwayland layer icons can't be generated right away. I use the window-created event which triggers instantly when an app is opened.
        Therefore, to compensate for this, we need to wait. How much? I'm not sure. On my PC 200ms works great, but some PCs may need longer which is why this option exists.
      </description>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>
